This Koshinage, or hip throw, is going to be from a hook strike, or Yokimunuchi.
Daniel's going to blast me to the side of the head.
This is a very dynamic Kushinage, because I have to blend with the oncoming strike, and time myself so I can end up on his hip at the same time.
So you need to end up in here.
What I'm going to do is come in and dominate here.
He's already spinning in this motion, so all I need to do is plant my hip there and draw him over.
Here, here's my hip, I'm already in position, and away we go.
There's a couple tricky things about this.
Is when I do this, I don't want to step way out here, because I'm really out of center.
I only want to step, here, almost stepping on his foot, that allows me to get good position.
Now he's already bleeding out, there's nowhere for that foot to go, I can draw him into my hips.
Here, I've trapped.
It's here, he's trapped.
Now we'll go ahead and get on the hip.
Here I am, locked up in the hip; he's already falling, put my hip into it, over we go.
Let's do that one more time.
Blending with it, hooking the hip.
That's Koshinage, the hip throw, from a hook strike, Yokimunuchi.